{
    "id": "72ec5a9699af49a0a2f928ada5372f10",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We must leave now, …………………………?",
            "description": "If the main sentence has an auxiliary verb, it is repeated in the question tag. ",
            "answers": [
                "should we",
                "mustn't we",
                "shouldn't we"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The children were playing outside, …………………………..?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative statements.",
            "answers": [
                "were they",
                "weren't they",
                "was they"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The wise man can solve our problem, ………………………….?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative statements. ",
            "answers": [
                "can't he",
                "can he",
                "won't he"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am working hard, …………………………….?",
            "description": "The question tag for I am is aren’t I?",
            "answers": [
                "am I",
                "amn't I",
                "aren't I"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the winner of the prize, ……………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are you",
                "aren't you",
                "weren't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "One picture is worth a thousand words, ………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "wasn't it"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nothing can happen, ……………………………?",
            "description": "Nothing is a negative word hence an affirmative tag is used after it. In tags, we use it to refer to nothing.",
            "answers": [
                "can it",
                "can nothing",
                "can't nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody wanted a drink, ……………………………?",
            "description": "In tags we use they to refer to somebody/anybody.",
            "answers": [
                "did somebody",
                "did they",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is quite good, ………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "doesn't it"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a sister, …………………………..?",
            "description": "When have refers to a state, question tags with have and do are both possible.",
            "answers": [
                "hasn't she",
                "doesn't she",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Shut up, …………………………..?",
            "description": "After imperatives, we use will/would/can/can’t/could you? to ask people to do things.",
            "answers": [
                "can't you",
                "will you",
                "would you",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "She works here, ………………………….?",
            "description": "When the given sentence is in the simple present tense, we use do/does in the tag.",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "does she",
                "doesn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}